Inventory of the Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
Department of Special Collections
- Russica Book Shop / "Russica Book and Art Shop, Inc." (New York) [14 of 17], 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  Contains catalogs / bulletins no. 2-5 and two identical unnumbered catalogs; 8 items total (including doubles). Multilingual. Names: Valery Kuharets.
- Russica Book Shop / "Russica Book and Art Shop, Inc." (New York) [15 of 17], 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs / bulletins no. 5A-6,8-9,10A-11 and related materials; 11 items total (including doubles). Multilingual. Names: Valery Kuharets.
- Russica Book Shop / "Russica Book and Art Shop, Inc." (New York) [16 of 17], 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  Contains book lists / catalogs no. 5 (two different catalogs), 6-8; some with handwritten notes / marks. In English and Russian (both in Cyrillic and Latin transliteration). Names: Valery Kuharets.
- Russica Book Shop / "Russica Book and Art Shop, Inc." (New York) [17 of 17], 1981; n.d. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  Contains price lists / catalogs no. 50, 51 (two different catalogs), 52, some with handwritten notes / marks; 4 items total. In English and Russian (in Latin transliteration). Names: Valery Kuharets.
- Russica Publishers / "Russica Book and Art Shop, Inc." (Berlin-New York), 1979; 11.19.2005; 04.25.2006 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  Contains 5 leaflets (price lists and releases), 2 e-mail printouts; 7 items total (including doubles). In English and Russian (both in Cyrillic and Latin transliteration). Names: Valery J. Cool-Kulakov.
- La Russie Illustrée (Paris), 1936 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  Contains a newsletter / press release in Russian (pre-revolutionary spelling).
- Sabo / Sabov, [?] (Florida), n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  Contains 3 typewritten annotated price lists, in Russian (both original and in Latin transliteration) and English.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [1 of 8], 1978-1979; 1985-1988; 1991; 1996; n.d. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  Contains typewritten and handwritten correspondence, price lists, catalogs, memos, financial documents, related materials, a clipping; 12 items total. Some materials are in Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [2 of 8], 1978-1979; 1981; n.d. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  Contains typewritten price lists and photocopies no. 2, 3 (two different items), 4-5, 7, 9-11, 16 (two identical items), 17-19; some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [3 of 8], 1983 [?]; 1986-1987; n.d. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  Contains typewritten price lists and photocopies no. 27, 38, 52-54, 55 (two identical issues), 56 (two identical issues), 57, 58 (two identical issues), 59-62; some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [4 of 8], 1988-1989; n.d. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  Contains typewritten price lists no. 64-76, 77 (two identical issues), 78-81; some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [5 of 8], 1990; n.d. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  Contains typewritten price lists and photocopies no. 83-98; some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [6 of 8], n.d. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  Contains typewritten price lists no. 99-104, 105 (two identical issues), 106; some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [7 of 8], 1997; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  Contains typewritten price lists no. 107-111, 113-118 and related materials; some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Saint Petersbourg. Antiquités et Livres Russes (Paris) [8 of 8], 2001; 2003; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  Contains typewritten price lists no. 119-121, 122 (two identical issues), 123-124; no. 1, 2 (two identical issues); some are annotated. In Russian. Names: Wojciech Zalewski, I.M.Lempert, Lazar Fleishman.
- Salzmann, Zdenek (Amherst, MA), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  Contains a typewritten price list and a photocopy of another one. In Czech and Slovak [?].
- Samizdat Archive Association (Munich, Germany), 1977; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  Contains 2 identical leaflets, a press release and 2 order forms.
- Sarnacki, J., Polish-American Directory, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  Contains a list of Polish book dealers in US, Canada and Europe; a photocopy of a typewritten document, 2 pages, with numerous handwritten marks and notes.
- Saur, K.G., Bulletin (Ohio), June 2000 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Savine [Savin], Andrei V., (Paris), 1992 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  Contains and envelope and a photocopy of a typewritten inventory of the savin's archival collection, 72 pages total, in Russian. Names: Kopaneva, N.
- Scharf, Arthur, Books (Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania), Jan 27, 1981; March 2, 1981; May 27, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  Contains 2 catalogs and a reply form. Multilingual.
- Schlacks, Charles, Jr., Publisher (Los Angeles, CA), Autumn 1994; April 12, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  Contains a leaflet / catalog and a photocopy of a press release, 2 pages.
- Scholarly Resources, Inc. (Delaware), May 12, 1999; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  Contains 2 catalogs, an order form and a typewritten letter with a handwritten signature, 1 page. Multilingual.
- Scholz, Bernd E., M.A. (Marburg), March 20, 1985; 1991; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  Contains a catalog, a press release with a handwritten note on it, and a typewritten letter, 1 page. Multilingual.
- Schwarz,, Thomas F., Bookseller (Mill Valley, CA), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Scientia / "Scientia. Old and New Books" / "Scientia Antiquariat Aalen" (Zutphen, The Netherlands), Jan 17, 1985; June 10, 1986; March 1997; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  Contains 2 catalogs, one typewritten catalog / price list, and a postcard / order form. Multilingual.
- Scientific Russian Translating Services, Dec 29, 1977; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  Contains typewritten price lists and photocopies of price lists, some with handwritten marks / notes, 4 items total. Multilingual.
- Seluzicki, Charles, Rare and Fine Books (Portland, Oregon), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Services Complets d'Édition (Quebec, Canada), Jan 18, 1987; Jan 29, 1988; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  Contains a typewritten price list, photocopies of related documents and clippings, correspondence etc., 5 items total, some with handwritten notes / marks. Multilingual.
- Seydi, Sevin (London), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Shanghai Trade Directory, 1939; 12.04.1997; n.d. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  Contains materials regarding book trade in Shanghai, printouts and photocopies, some with handwritten marks / notes, 7 items total.
- S.R. Shapiro, Book for Libraries (New York), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  Contains typewritten price lists and photocopies, 5 items total, multilingual.
- Shevchenko Scientific Society, Inc. (New York), 1980 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Shmavonian, Sarkis, Books and Prints (Berkeley, CA), 1985 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  Contains a typewritten price list with a press release and a handwritten note, 6 pages total.
- Sien Otechestva, Russian Cooperative Progressive Semi-Weekly Newspaper (New York), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  Contains a photocopy of a clipping, 1 page.
- Sigma Publishing (Toronto, Canada), Feb. 1998; n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  Contains a magazine and a release with an envelope. In Hungarian and English.
- SK-IMPEX, Joint-Stock Company (Moscow), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Slavia Art Books (St. Petersburg / Leningrad), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Slavia Library (State College, PA), 1982; 1987-1989; n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs and photocopies of catalogs, 8 items total (including doubles). In Russian and Ukrainian (in Latin transliteration).
- Slavica Export-Import (Warsaw, Poland), Sept. 1996 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Slavica Publishers, Inc. (Columbia, Ohio), Autumn 1982; Sept. 1986; Nov. 1987; March 1989; Jan. 1990; April 1990; Oct. 1990; Sept. 1991; Nov. 1993; Jan. 1995; April 1997 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  Contains 12 catalogs (including doubles); some with handwritten notes and marks.
- Slavonic Bazaar (New York), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  Contains a press release / leaflet, in Russian.
- Slawistyczny O?rodek Wydawniczy (Warsaw, Poland), 1991 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  Contains a catalog, in Polish and English mostly.
- Sliabhair (Bethesda, MD), Dec 1985; Jan 1987; n.d. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  Contains leaflets / price lists and a press release, 1 page; 5 items total. In Bulgarian, Hungarian, and English mostly.
- Slienger, Carl, Specialist Publisher and Antiquarian Bookseller (London), July 14, 2006; n.d. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  Contains typewritten and printed catalogs, price lists, and press releases; 8 items total. Multilingual.
- Slog (Jerusalem), Spring 1992; 02.03.1993 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  Contains a handwritten price list in Russian, 2 pages, and a catalog with handwritten notes and marks, in Russian.
- Slovak National Library, 11.11.2002 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  Contains a typewritten acknowledgment receipt, 1 page, in Slovak and English.
- Slovo, The Publishing House" (Berlin), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  Contains 2 identical leaflets in Russian (old spelling) and a gift search slip.
- Smart Link Corporation (USA-Russia), n.d. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  Contains a CD-ROM, Volume no.1
- Smitskamp Oriental Antiquarium (Leiden, The Netherlands), Oct 2004 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  Contains a multilingual catalog with a handwritten note attached.
- Smolders, Wilhelm (Vienna, Austria) [1 of 4], 1979-1988; n.d. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  Contains price lists, business correspondence, related materials, some heavily annotated and / or damaged. 69 items total, multilingual.
- Smolders, Wilhelm (Vienna, Austria) [2 of 4], n.d. (Box 64, Folder 18)
  Contains catalogs ("extra lists") no. 27-29, with handwritten marks and notes. Multilingual.
- Smolders, Wilhelm (Vienna, Austria) [3 of 4], n.d. (Box 64, Folder 19)
  Contains price lists ("special offers") no. 36, 40-44, 45 (2 copies), 46-49, 52, 60, with handwritten notes / marks, multilingual.
- Smolders, Wilhelm (Vienna, Austria) [4 of 4], 1979-1980; n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs ("lists") no 43, 44 (2 copies), 45-49, 54 (2 copies), 57, 59, 61-62, 64, with handwritten notes / marks, multilingual.
- Sofia Books (Bulgaria), Sept 2005; 09.23.2008 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  Contains a catalog and an e-mail printout, 1 page. In Bulgarian and English mostly.
- Soiuz russkikh izdatelei i knigoprodavtsev v Germanii (Germany), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  Contains a photocopy of a catalog's front cover, 1 page. In Russian.
- Soiuzpechat', The Agency (Moscow), 1996, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Sonnewald Heckenhauer, Antiquariat der Wissenschaft (Mengen-Ennetach, Germany), Sept 18, 1979; March 18, 1985; Feb 3, 1987; n.d. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs, correspondence and related materials; 7 items total, including doubles. Multilingual.
- Sotheby Parke Bernet and Co. (London) [1 of 2], 1969; 1980-1981; n.d. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  Contains catalogs, price lists and related documents, 5 items total. Multilingual.
- Sotheby Parke Bernet and Co. (London) [2 of 2], 1975 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Henry Sotheran Limited (London), Winter 1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  Contains a photocopied fragment of a catalog with handwritten notes and marks, 4 pages total.
- Spo?eczny Instytut Wydawniczy Znak (Kraków, Poland), Jan 1990 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  Contains a catalog in Polish, with handwritten notes and marks.
- Srbica Books (Yugoslavica) (Toronto, Ontario), Spring 1994; Spring 1995; Spring-Summer 1996 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, correspondence, related materials, 4 items total. Multilingual.
- St. Martin's Press (New York), 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- St. Vladimir's Seminary Press (Crestwood, NY), 1997-1998 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Státní knihovna ČSR / State Library, Czech Republic, Nov 1987 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog in Czech.
- Richard Stoddard, Performing Arts Books (New York), Sept. 28, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Stodieck's Buchhandlung (Berlin), Winter 1985/1986 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog with enclosures, in Polish and German mostly.
- Stroganov, I.I. (Beograd), 1931 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  Contains 2 photocopies from the almanac "Russkaia emigratsiia, 1920-1930 gg.", Vypusk 1, Beograd, 1931; materials are related to Russian émigré book trade and cultural life in Yugoslavia.
- Studio Bibliografico Fortuna (Firenze, Italy), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Svaz českých knihkupců a nakladatelů (Prague, Czech Republic), 1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Swets International (Moscow), 1999 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- E. Sztein's Antiquary (Orange, CT) [1 of 4], n.d. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  Contains price lists and catalogs, press releases, and related materials, typewritten and photocopied (including photocopies of 1910-1920s materials); some documents with handwritten notes and marks. In Russian and English mostly, 20 items total.
- E. Sztein's Antiquary (Orange, CT) [2 of 4], n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  Contains price lists and catalogs, press releases, and related materials, typewritten and photocopied (including photocopies of 1910-1920s materials); some documents with handwritten notes and marks. In Russian and English mostly, 15 items total.
- E. Sztein's Antiquary (Orange, CT) [3 of 4], 1981-1989 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  Contains price lists and catalogs, invoices, correspondence, and related materials (typewritten, handwritten, and photocopied; some are annotated). In Russian, Polish, and English mostly, 40 items total.
- E. Sztein's Antiquary (Orange, CT) [4 of 4], 1990-1994; 2000 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  Contains price lists and catalogs, invoices, correspondence, and related materials (typewritten, handwritten, and photocopied; some are annotated). In Russian, Polish, and English mostly, 15 items total.
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [1 of 25], n.d. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  Contains typewritten and photocopied price lists, a leaflet, and related materials; some are damaged and / or incomplete, some are annotated; 8 items total, multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [2 of 25], 1969; 1974-1975; 1976-1977; 1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, and related correspondence, typewritten, printed, and photocopied; some are annotated; 6 items total, multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [3 of 25], 1979-1982 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, and related correspondence, typewritten, printed, and photocopied; some are annotated; a photocopy of a clipping in Polish, 1 page; 15 items total, multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [4 of 25], 1983-1985 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, releases, and related correspondence, typewritten, printed, and photocopied; some are annotated; 23 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [5 of 25], 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  Contains printed catalogs, invoices, and related materials; some are annotated; 16 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [6 of 25], 1986-1988 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and photocopies of clippings; 11 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [7 of 25], 1988 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  Contains printed and typewritten catalogs / price lists; some are annotated; 9 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [8 of 25], 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  Contains printed and typewritten catalogs / price lists; some are annotated; 7 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [9 of 25], 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists; 11 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [10 of 25], 1990-1991 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists; 9 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [11 of 25], 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  Contains typewritten price lists, purchase orders, receipts, correspondence; 72 items total; some materials are annotated and / or slightly damaged. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [12 of 25], 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists, invoices, and related materials; 7 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [13 of 25], 1993 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  Contains typewritten price lists, purchase orders, receipts, correspondence, related materials; 73 items total; some materials are annotated and / or slightly damaged. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [14 of 25], 1993 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  Contains typewritten price lists, receipts, correspondence, related materials; 15 items total; some materials are annotated and / or slightly damaged. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [15 of 25], 1992-1994 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  Contains typewritten price lists (originals and copies), correspondence, related materials; 61 items total; some materials are annotated and / or slightly damaged. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [16 of 25], 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies; 10 items total, multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [17 of 25], 1994 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, related materials; 5 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [18 of 25], 1994-1995 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, purchase orders, correspondence, invoices and receipts, clippings, releases, related materials; some annotated and / or damaged; 83 items total, multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [19 of 25], 1995 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, correspondence, invoices and receipts, related materials; some annotated and / or damaged; 43 items total, multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [20 of 25], 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, some incomplete; 4 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [21 of 25], 1996 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies; 9 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [22 of 25], 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, invoices and receipts, purchase orders, correspondence; 16 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [23 of 25], 1998 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, 5 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [24 of 25], 1998 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and copies, 8 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Szwede Slavic Books (Palo Alto, California) [25 of 25], 1998-1999; 2003; 2004 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  Contains printed and typewritten catalogs / price lists and copies, 8 items total (including doubles), multilingual. Names: Yuri Felshtinsky, "American Help Co.".
- Štatistický iúrad Slovenskej republiky (Slovenia), Dec 1999 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  Contains a catalog in Slovenian.
- B. Šwiderski. Polish Book House (London), 1955-1960; 1962; no date (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Contains catalogs / price lists, releases and related materials, 32 items total, in Polish and English mostly.
- Tarasenkov, Dmitry (Fairfax, VA), 1986-1988; no date (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Contains typewritten price lists, annotated, 5 items total, in Russian mostly.
- V. Tarasov (Jerusalem), 1988-1990; 1997; no date (Box 71, Folder 2)
  Contains typewritten and printed catalogs / price lists and related materials (correspondence, invoices etc.), 11 items total (including doubles), some annotated, some materials are in Russian.
- Tchikovani, Shaliko (Paris), Sept 21, 2000; no date (Box 71, Folder 3)
  Contains typewritten catalogs / lists in Russian and a business letter in English, 6 items total.
- Thornton's of Oxford - Booksellers and Publishers since 1835 (Oxford) [1 of ], 1984-1987; 1990 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists, releases and related documents; 12 items total (including doubles), some annotated. Multilingual.
- Thornton's of Oxford - Booksellers and Publishers since 1835 (Oxford) [2 of ], 1991-1997 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  Contains printed catalogs / price lists and related materials; 25 items total (including doubles), some annotated. Multilingual.
- Thornton's of Oxford - Booksellers and Publishers since 1835 (Oxford) [3 of ], 2002-2002; 2006; no date (Box 71, Folder 6)
  Contains typewritten and printed price lists, e-mail printouts, releases, posters, and related materials; 23 items total (including doubles), some annotated. Multilingual.
- Thornton's of Oxford - Booksellers and Publishers since 1835 (Oxford) [4 of ], no date (Box 71, Folder 7)
  Contains printed catalogs, 18 items total (including doubles), some with handwritten notes. Multilingual.
- Thornton's of Oxford - Booksellers and Publishers since 1835 (Oxford) [5 of 5], no date (Box 71, Folder 8)
  Contains printed catalogs, releases, and related materials; 26 items total (including doubles). Multilingual.
- Timofejeff, N. A. / "Possev-Antiquariat" (Rome, Italy) [1 of 5], 1978; 1985-1986; no date (Box 71, Folder 9)
  Contains correspondence, price lists and related documents, 5 items total, in Russian and English.
- Timofejeff, N. A. / "Possev-Antiquariat" (Rome, Italy) [2 of 5], 1978 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  Contains typewritten annotated price lists and correspondence, 6 items total, in Russian mostly. Some materials are damaged.
- Timofejeff, N. A. / "Possev-Antiquariat" (Rome, Italy) [3 of 5], 1980-1984; no date (Box 72, Folder 1)
  Contains typewritten annotated price lists, 15 items total, in Russian mostly.
- Timofejeff, N. A. / "Possev-Antiquariat" (Rome, Italy) [4 of 5], 1985; 1996; no date (Box 72, Folder 2)
  Contains typewritten annotated price lists, 11 items total, in Russian mostly.
- Timofejeff, N. A. / "Possev-Antiquariat" (Rome, Italy) [5 of 5], 1987-1993; no date (Box 72, Folder 3)